EMRE EKICI

COMPUTER SCIENTIST

CONTACT

+32 491 93 06 19

emre.ekici2a@gmail.com

Huidevettersstraat 84-1, 3530

SKILLS

Java, Python, C#

Docker, Kubernetes

MySQL, MariaDB, SQLite

HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Laravel

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Applied Computer Science

Thomas More Hogeschool

2021-

*Still continuing education

Bachelor of International Relations

Uludag University

2015-2020

LANGUAGES

English

Turkish



Dutch



PROFILE

I am a very ambitious and driven person. I constantly strive for improvement and betterment. After completing my international relations degree and working for ~2 years in related fields, I realized I wanted to pursue an education in the computer sciences. I have experience in working in multi-cultural environments and team settings. I am an open-minded person and have strong communicational skills. I am set to graduate in June of 2024 and hope to find employment in either ERP consultancy or data analysis.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Foreign Trade Operations Specialist

2020-2021

FCA Turkey Tofas

- Organized import/export operations for spare parts from and to Italy and France
- Created a performance evaluation system to determine efficiency and calculate most cost effective transportation methods and logistics firms.
- Tracked inventory of empty cases used during import and was tasked with allocating these cases for export processes'.

Import/Export Accounting Intern

FCA Turkey Tofas

2019-2020

- Processed invoices from both domestic and foreign companies using SAP.
- Tasked with ensuring invoices being paid by due dates.
- Contacted firms every quarter to reconcile account balances, in cases where a dispute was present, I would be tasked with investigating and resolving te disputes.
- Tasked with organizing and archiving important files which needed to be kept as paper copies.
- Tasked with preparing files and documents for financial inspections.